<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
	<ST_FrogRole>Primary Frog Role</ST_FrogRole>
	<ST_FrogRoleSecondary>Secondary Frog Role</ST_FrogRoleSecondary>
	<ST_FrogRoleTertiary>Tertiary Frog Role</ST_FrogRoleTertiary>
	<ST_FrogRarity>Frog Rarity</ST_FrogRarity>



	<!-- Roles -->
	<ST_FrogFoodProduction>Food Production</ST_FrogFoodProduction>	
	<ST_FrogProduction>Production</ST_FrogProduction>	
	<ST_MeleeTank>Melee Tank</ST_MeleeTank>	
	<ST_FrogPoison>Poison</ST_FrogPoison>	
	<ST_FrogRanged>Ranged</ST_FrogRanged>	
	<ST_FrogLick>Lick</ST_FrogLick>	
	<ST_FrogFire>Fire</ST_FrogFire>
	<ST_FrogIntelligent>Draftable</ST_FrogIntelligent>	
	<ST_FrogExplosive>Explosive</ST_FrogExplosive>	
	<ST_FrogFriendly>Friendly</ST_FrogFriendly>	
	<ST_FrogDivine>Archotech</ST_FrogDivine>	
	<ST_FrogCarrier>Carrier</ST_FrogCarrier>
	<TSP_ST_FrogNormal>Normal</TSP_ST_FrogNormal>
	<TSP_ST_Frog_NA>Non-applicable</TSP_ST_Frog_NA>
	<TSP_ST_FrogMachine>Mechanoid</TSP_ST_FrogMachine>
	<TSP_ST_FrogEnemy>Hostile</TSP_ST_FrogEnemy>
	<TSP_ST_FrogSapient>Sapient</TSP_ST_FrogSapient>
	<TSP_ST_Frog_BORPA>Borpa</TSP_ST_Frog_BORPA>
	<TSP_ST_Frog_JOHNBORPA>Demon</TSP_ST_Frog_JOHNBORPA>
	<TSP_ST_Frog_KACHOW>Speed</TSP_ST_Frog_KACHOW>

	<TSP_ST_FrogNormalDesc>This is merely a frog. It bares no unique characteristics or abilities, and lacks utilty beyond an ordinary animal.</TSP_ST_FrogNormalDesc>
	<TSP_ST_Frog_NA_Desc>N/A</TSP_ST_Frog_NA_Desc>
	<ST_FrogFoodProductionDesc>This frog naturally produces a resource which can be used as food.</ST_FrogFoodProductionDesc>
	<TSP_ST_FrogMachineDesc>This frog has a neural up-link to the Mechanoid Hive! It will behave as a Mechanoid and engage in hostile combat with your colonists! It cannot be tamed or reasoned with, so kill it quickly!</TSP_ST_FrogMachineDesc>
	<TSP_ST_FrogEnemyDesc>This frog is a man hunter and will attack anything it sees!</TSP_ST_FrogEnemyDesc>
	<TSP_ST_FrogSapientDesc>This frog is sapient: it is fully capable of human-level intellect, thought, and reasoning.</TSP_ST_FrogSapientDesc>
	<ST_FrogProductionDesc>This frog naturally produces a non-food resource.</ST_FrogProductionDesc>	
	<ST_MeleeTankDesc>This frog is tougher than most and is capable of withstanding large amounts of damage during melee combat.</ST_MeleeTankDesc>	
	<ST_FrogPoisonDesc>This frog utilizes poison attacks in combat.</ST_FrogPoisonDesc>	
	<ST_FrogRangedDesc>This frog utilizes ranged attacks in combat</ST_FrogRangedDesc>	
	<ST_FrogLickDesc>This frog utilizes lick attacks in combat.</ST_FrogLickDesc>	
	<ST_FrogFireDesc>This frog utilizes fire attacks in combat.</ST_FrogFireDesc>	
	<ST_FrogIntelligentDesc>This frog can be Drafted like a colonist and ordered to attack accordingly!</ST_FrogIntelligentDesc>	
	<ST_FrogExplosiveDesc>This frog explodes on death!</ST_FrogExplosiveDesc>	
	<ST_FrogFriendlyDesc>This frog is extremely friendly and improves the mood of those around it in some way. It may do this by a special Hediff that touches the heart of those nearby, or it simply really likes to rapidly nuzzle the ones it loves.</ST_FrogFriendlyDesc>	
	<ST_FrogDivineDesc>This frog originated from a fully realized Archotech on a Transcendant World. Its biology, abilities, and functions are inconceivable to any sapient race or Personae Core. \n \n All Transcendent worlds go silent, but one, the world of Poobah, continues to send out ships full of Flying Frogs with no understandable reason. \n The saying goes: "From this point on, a Transcendant World Archotech's motivations are unknowable to us, the same way our motivations are unknowable to an ant."</ST_FrogDivineDesc>
	<ST_FrogCarrierDesc>This frog is very large and can be used as a pack animal.</ST_FrogCarrierDesc>
	<TSP_ST_Frog_BORPA_Desc>This is a Borpa: a special, spinning frog that ruined a bald man's life. Borpas are notably affectionate and useful in multiple roles.</TSP_ST_Frog_BORPA_Desc>
	<TSP_ST_Frog_JOHNBORPA_Desc>This frog is John Borpa manifest on the mortal plane. He is a magnificent, nearly invincible demon with health so high that nothing short of a nuclear weapon can kill him. He will leave in a day or two. Pray that no one is caught outside.</TSP_ST_Frog_JOHNBORPA_Desc>
	<TSP_ST_Frog_KACHOW_Desc>Speed. This frog is speed. No terrain can slow him down.</TSP_ST_Frog_KACHOW_Desc>




	<!-- Rarities -->
	<ST_FrogCommon>Common</ST_FrogCommon>
	<ST_FrogUncommon>Uncommon</ST_FrogUncommon>
	<ST_FrogRare>Rare</ST_FrogRare>
	<ST_FrogLegendary>Legendary</ST_FrogLegendary>
	<ST_FrogAbomination>Genetic Experiment</ST_FrogAbomination>
	<TSP_ST_FrogCommonality_Hostile>Man Hunter</TSP_ST_FrogCommonality_Hostile>

	<ST_FrogCommonDesc>This frog comes from a fairly common species.</ST_FrogCommonDesc>
	<ST_FrogUncommonDesc>This frog is not commonly seen in the wild.</ST_FrogUncommonDesc>
	<ST_FrogRareDesc>This frog is quite rare. Treasure it.</ST_FrogRareDesc>
	<ST_FrogLegendaryDesc>This is truly a frog for the ages, a legend whose story will echo on into eternity.</ST_FrogLegendaryDesc>
	<ST_FrogAbominationDesc>This frog is the product of genetic experimentation and does not occur naturally in the wild.</ST_FrogAbominationDesc>
	<TSP_ST_FrogCommonality_Hostile_Desc>This frog is a hostile man hunter! Any occurence in the wild is an immediate threat to life and limb!</TSP_ST_FrogCommonality_Hostile_Desc>
</LanguageData>