<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<TipSetDef>
		<defName>StorytimeTips</defName>
		<tips>
			<li TKey="Quote1">On the Rim, most racist things are true.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote2">The first step to winning is admitting that you suck.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote3">Shhh... its vision is based off of sight.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote4">We should car bomb friendlies.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote5">Don't talk.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote6">Brethren before wenches.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote7">How would a car do the Nazi salute?</li>
			<li TKey="Quote8">If you eat one more burrito, I'm putting you in the ground.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote9">Who here spits on old people for fun?</li>
			<li TKey="Quote10">What is the half-life of a coconut?</li>
			<li TKey="Quote11">Psst... do you want to buy a gun?</li>
			<li TKey="Quote12">Dimensions are a lot like old people.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote13">The greatest 'Rimworld' players have long since purged themselves of any emotion but animal rage.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote14">"Let's bomb the Hogwarts Express," said Harry.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote15">The babies look like mushrooms.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote16">Here on the Rim, people generally aren't that valuable compared to items.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote17">I wouldn't spit on you if you were dying.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote18">Mike Pence serves Tom Bombadil.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote19">The point is that five years ago, in September, there was something else out there...</li>
			<li TKey="Quote20">Why create what you can steal? Raiders know this!</li>
			<li TKey="Quote21">Roots are in the dirt where they belong.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote22">I AM the missing arm.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote23">The pickle is my spirit animal.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote24">'Rimworld' players feed on human suffering.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote25">I have level one Moon Jukes.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote26">Just because they talk doesn't mean they feel pain.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote27">Let's go pistol-whip a Muffalo with a BB gun.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote28">Jonah has officially had his racist status revoked as of 9:20 PM, July 17, 2013 AD.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote29">Martha Stewart did nothing wrong.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote30">I am going to cut my own legs off so I can run at peak efficiency.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote31">Let's lynch a Pikmin.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote32">'Rimworld' players want to sucker punch babies.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote29">Organ harvester is a master of gaslighting.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote30">The Council of the Poobah Society will decide your fate.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote31">Dedicated kill boxes are for weenies. Use choke points, take cover, build walls, and employ corridors between buildings like a real man.</li>
			<!-- Too political -->
			<!-- <li TKey="Quote32">LET'S GO BRANDON!</li> -->
			<!-- Might reflect badly on me even if it's hilarious -->
			<!-- <li TKey="Quote32">"Man, poor Fritz... do they remember him as Fritz the wall builder? No. Do they remember him as Fritz, unbeatable at horseshoes? No, they dont. It seems if you go to town with just one Megascarab, suddenly you are Fritz the Megascarab lover until the end of time."</li> -->
			<li TKey="Quote32">Attach the homing beacon to the Sheep!</li>
			<li TKey="Quote33">If you have the Alpha Biomes Mod or the Rimefeller Mod, you can fuel the Alloy Blast Furnace with Propane or Crude Oil!</li>
			<li TKey="Quote34">-and maybe that's the way for us to end...</li>
			<li TKey="Quote35">That's an interesting point. However, your mother.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote36">Look upon my works, ye mighty, and despair.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote38">How did you even get that motorcycle ON the high dive, Tanner?</li>
			<li TKey="Quote39">Who's that GIIIIIGGLING in the background, Ian?</li>
			<li TKey="Quote40">Spencer, you're the only one that's got a fez with a propeller on it!</li>
			<li TKey="Quote41">Please induct TurtleShroom into the Poobah Society, Isengriff!</li>
			<li TKey="Quote42">When gnome flour is harvested, it is not used as a general cooking ingredient. However, it can be designated as such at any Bench that can grind Gnome Root poppies.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote43">There is no war on Rata Jeub.</li>
			<li TKey="Quote44">You took the donkey home! So you don't get unemployment benefits!</li>
			<li TKey="Quote45">Make sure to place the Alloying Blast Furnace indoors!</li>
			<li TKey="Quote46">The Grinder is incorporated with numerous Mods! Over forty recipes from other Mods are supported, including the Morrowrim Mod, the Vanilla Cooking Expanded Mod, the Underground Food Mod, the Tradtional Chinese Mod, and more!</li>
		</tips>
	</TipSetDef>
</Defs>