<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Defs>  <ThingDef ParentName="ResourceBase">    <defName>Weezer</defName>    <label>Weezer albums</label>    <description>A cluster of musical albums encoded by laser on an eons-old, physical optical disc standard, each comprised principally of poly-carbonate plastics. The age of these albums is estimated to be three thousand years old, and they are socketed into plastic cases, each baring pictures of Old Earth humans in late twentieth-century clothing. \n \n Written on the intact cases and optical discs is "WEEZER", indicating the subject and creator of the musical album. These albums are diverse and span Weezer's lifetime of musical production. Weezer was an alternative rock and roll band that existed on Old Earth millinea ago. "Alternative rock and roll" was a term developed at the end of the twentieth century to separate mainstream rock and roll from lesser and less sponsored, independent rock and roll producing studioes. \n Over the course of over thirty years, Weezer published multiple albums, initially on poly-carbonate optical discs, and later in the familiar digital encoding used in all music since the early twenty-first century, up to the present day. \n \n Weezer's music was never a staple of human civilization at its time and gained only mild popularity, unlike some peer bands. However, in the twenty-fourth century, it developed a massive following among the Core World and Urb World populations of the Gnome subspecies of human, who accidentally uncovered the ancient albums. \n Over the next thousand years, Gnomes from high-tech planets would distribute Weezer's music across all of galactic civilization, mostly to their fellow Gnomes, and the saturation eventually allowed Gnomes with even Medieval Tech Levels to acquire them. \n \n On this particular part of the Galactim Rim, this Rim World's Gnome population has successfully been given the sheet music and lyrics to the multitude of Weezer's songs. They sing Weezer songs at the courts of their gnoblemen and in every day life, with the music being an integral part of their culture. \n \n They will be more than happy to sing them to your civilization, too!</description>    <graphicData>      <texPath>Things/Items/Resources/Ores/Weezer</texPath>      <graphicClass>Graphic_StackCount</graphicClass>    </graphicData>	<uiIconPath>UI/ItemIcons/Weezer_Icon</uiIconPath>    <statBases>      <MarketValue>5</MarketValue>      <Mass>0.2</Mass>      <StuffPower_Armor_Sharp>0.8</StuffPower_Armor_Sharp>      <StuffPower_Armor_Blunt>0.4</StuffPower_Armor_Blunt>      <StuffPower_Armor_Heat>0</StuffPower_Armor_Heat>      <StuffPower_Insulation_Cold>15</StuffPower_Insulation_Cold>      <StuffPower_Insulation_Heat>15</StuffPower_Insulation_Heat>      <SharpDamageMultiplier>1</SharpDamageMultiplier>      <BluntDamageMultiplier>1.1</BluntDamageMultiplier>    </statBases>    <useHitPoints>false</useHitPoints>    <thingCategories>		<li>Manufactured</li>		<!--		<li>ResourcesRaw</li>		<li>Textiles</li>		-->    </thingCategories>    <deepCommonality>2.8</deepCommonality>    <deepCountPerPortion>60</deepCountPerPortion>    <deepLumpSizeRange>9~10</deepLumpSizeRange>    <stuffProps>      <categories>        <li>Metallic</li>		<li>Fabric</li>		<li>Woody</li>		<li MayRequire="Dubwise.Rimefeller">Plastic</li>		<li MayRequire="Dubwise.Rimefeller">Composite</li>		<li MayRequire="sarg.alphabiomes">AB_ExoticMetals</li>      </categories>	  <stuffAdjective>Weezer</stuffAdjective>      <commonality>0.1</commonality>      <color>(0, 182, 213)</color>      <statFactors>        <MaxHitPoints>2.25</MaxHitPoints>        <Beauty>2</Beauty>        <Flammability>0.5</Flammability>        <WorkToMake>0.4</WorkToMake>        <WorkToBuild>0.9</WorkToBuild>      </statFactors>    </stuffProps>    <terrainAffordanceNeeded>Light</terrainAffordanceNeeded>  </ThingDef>    <ThingDef>    <defName>GroundWeezer</defName>    <label>Weezer Error Log Fix</label>    <description>This should NEVER be visible in the game.</description>	<thingClass>UnfinishedThing</thingClass>    <graphicData>      <texPath>UI/ItemIcons/Weezer_Icon</texPath>	  <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>	  <color>(255, 0, 0)</color>    </graphicData>    <statBases>      <MarketValue>0.001</MarketValue>      <Mass>0.001</Mass>    </statBases>    <useHitPoints>false</useHitPoints>    <thingCategories Inherit="False">    </thingCategories>    <terrainAffordanceNeeded>Light</terrainAffordanceNeeded>  </ThingDef></Defs>